Now, in this segment, we're going to talk about doing a front roll but instead of having the Frisbee right side up, it's actually going to be upside down.
We call that inverted.
Now, there's several different ways you can do that.
Actually, some people find this roll to be easier than the right side up roll.
With this one now the weight is on the bottom of the Frisbee.
So, you have to be kind of aware of that and again you want to start out by holding the Frisbee here.
Do a half a roll first and then you can do three quarters of a roll and then you can do a full roll.
Now, again you have to be nice and loose and have that Frisbee touch every single part of your arm.
You can also do the inverted roll coming up your arms and then back down the other side and if you notice I'm leaning back and then coming forward again, leaning back coming forward again, leaning back coming forward again.
That's the inverted roll.
The inverted roll can also be done with a lot of angle this way or it also can be done from a front roll to an inverted roll.